Hello there.
Let me ask, are you a financial services professional or licensed insurance agent
that has clients concerned about the future costs of long-term care
and where their care might be needed?
Maybe you're just someone concerned whether or not your assets will last
in the event of a chronic health challenge, and more importantly, what will be the consequences
to your family if and when long-term care is required in the future.
If you are either one and you don't know where to start,
consider taking this short online assessment.
The assessment can be customized, or it can be run incognito
without disclosing any personal contact or financial information.
In fact, once the assessment is completed, you can view it privately
and then download it to your personal computer or digital device.
No personal or financial information is retained
on any servers or this platform.
So go on and see for yourself how this tool could be helpful
in long-term care planning.
You'll be glad you did.
Oh, one more thing before I leave.
If you are in the insurance or financial services industry
and want to license and brand this tool, give us a call.
Our information is provided and viewable within the terms of use.
Thank you.